defenseone.com 2013-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Defense One

Last Updated: June 28, 2013

_Please note that our Sites and Mobile Content are under constant development. New services are added frequently and this agreement may therefore be modified and updated on an ongoing basis. It is important to check back to this page regularly._

At the Government Executive Media Group, a division of National Journal Group, Inc. ("Government Executive"), we want you to enjoy and benefit from our websites and online services secure in the knowledge that we have implemented fair information practices designed to protect your privacy. Our privacy policy below describes the information we collect, how we use it, and the choices you have regarding collection and use of your personal information. This policy applies to all websites and online services operated by Government Executive, including defenseone.com, governmentexecutive.com, nextgov.com, as well as to the content and services we provide to mobile users, through WAP and apps available on mobile devices such as Apple's iPhone and iPad (collectively, our "Sites" or "Sites and Mobile Content").

**What We Learn**

Our Sites may automatically recognize your domain name, IP address, browser version, operating system and the website you passed through to reach us. In addition, our Sites automatically gather certain usage information, like the numbers and frequency of visits to the Sites and their areas - very much like television ratings that tell how many people tuned in to a program. The information we obtain in providing Mobile Content varies depending on the practices of your device manufacturer, service provider, and choices available to you as a user.

Some features of our Sites do offer you the option of providing information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, phone number, organization, location, or any other identifying information. As described in greater detail below, such information will only be used to provide you with products or services you have requested or additional information about the Sites or their affiliates. (You may also provide us with such information in the course of subscribing to Government Executive magazine or other offerings from Government Executive - details of how we use such information are also provided below.)

Information gathered through the use of cookies is not used by our Sites to track any personally identifiable details.

**How We Use What We Learn**

The information we collect is used to improve the content of Government Executive magazine and our Sites and to keep you apprised of important developments. For example, we may use personally identifiable information to contact you as part of an online survey about our editorial offerings, inform you of material changes or additions to our services, advise you of account status, or contact you in order to comply with any legal requirements. Also, we compile and use your information so that we may keep you apprised of special offers, as well as additional products that may be of interest to you.

In some cases, we may share personally identifiable information to contact you (sometimes through a vendor or business partner) for the reasons we have described.

**What We Tell Others About You**

We will not sell or rent or willfully disclose any personally identifying information obtained through the Sites (other than in connection with magazine subscriptions ordered, as explained below) to a party outside Atlantic Media Company, its divisions, its affiliated publications (such as National Journal, National Journal Daily, The Atlantic, and NextGov), its vendors providing Internet hosting services, or third party list managers, without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifying information from our visitors, other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

From time to time we allow reputable companies, whose products or services we feel may interest our print subscribers, to contact these subscribers using the addresses provided to us during the process of subscribing to Government Executive's print edition. (We do not share these addresses directly with these companies, however - only with a third party who administers the process on our behalf.) . Many of our subscribers find this a valuable and time-saving service. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by letting us know by e-mailing, calling, or writing us (see addresses below).

We may provide statistical usage data in the aggregate--not information about you personally--to our partners about how visitors use the Sites. From time to time we conduct research on our users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information you provide to us upon registration, on order forms, as well as from our server log files or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis and we may share this aggregated data with advertisers or other businesses.

In some cases, we may disclose information about you to a third party if we are required to do so by law or if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law or legal process, to protect and defend our rights or to prevent misuse of our Sites, or to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

In the event of a corporate change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, or in the event of a sale of assets or a bankruptcy, Government Executive reserves the right to transfer your personally identifiable information to the new party in control or the party acquiring assets.

**What Are Cookies And How Do We Use Them?**

The Sites place a "cookie" on the browser of a user's computer to gather and store basic tracking information and to monitor the presentation of advertisements. We may also use the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as measuring certain traffic patterns. For example, cookies are used to ensure that you don't see the same ad too many times in a single session. Cookies are also used to restrict access to certain areas of the Sites to bona fide subscribers and to enable you to set up customized alerts that no other subscribers are permitted to see. Cookies are not related to any personally identifiable information and are not used to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie.

Advertising service vendors that serve ads into our Sites may also use their own cookies. You may opt-out of the cookies delivered by the Sites by changing the setting on your browser. Some browsers are set to refuse all cookies, or to restrict the conditions under which they are set. Please be aware that this will disable all cookies delivered to your browser, not just the ones delivered by us.  If you would like more information about advertisers' use of cookies, and about your ability not to accept these cookies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s Opt-Out page [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  If you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected during your visits to this or other sites, please visit the consumer opt-out page for the Self Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) (currently in beta).

Some online advertising for the Sites is delivered by the vendor DoubleClick, a Google company. For more information about DoubleClick's use of cookies, and to "opt-out" of the DoubleClick cookies, visit [www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy).

**Advertisers and Links**

The Sites contain links to other sites, including those produced by other organizations. Additionally, our advertisers, or Web sites that have links on our Sites, may also collect personally identifiable information directly from you. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of those sites. Please visit the sites of these businesses to review their privacy policies.

**Kids & Parents**

Kids under 13: Do not send us any information about yourself, such as your name, address, or e-mail address.

Parents: These Sites are not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13) and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 as part of the Sites. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 13 as part of the Sites without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such information from our records.

**Data Security**

We have in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. However, as effective as these measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, websites, or services, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

**What if I am a Non-U.S. User?**

Please note that the Sites are directed towards users who reside in the United States. It is not our intent to gather personally identifiable information from individuals residing outside of the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States whose laws may not provide the same level of protection for personal information as your home country. By using this web site, you consent to this transfer. You also consent to the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with this website in the federal and other courts of, and in accordance with the laws of, the District of Columbia.

**Disclaimer**

This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time at our discretion.

**How Can I Request that my Personally Identifiable Information not be Shared? How Can I Review My Personally Identifiable Information?**

As indicated above, if you do not want your personally identifiable information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by letting us know by e-mailing, calling or writing us (see addresses below). Similarly, please contact us at the same addresses if at any time you wish to review your personally identifiable information.

**Any Questions?**

For more information on our Privacy Policy, or if at any time you wish to discontinue receiving communications from us that do not directly pertain to your subscription, please let us know by emailing us, calling us at 202-739-8501, or writing to us at the address listed below.

**Our Postal Address**

Government Executive Media Group  
600 New Hampshire Avenue, NW  
Washington, DC 20037
